[
  {
    "question_number": 3,
    "question": "ما الكلمة المختلفة",
    "type": "اختيار",
    "choices": [
      "صداقة",
      "وفاء",
      "تضحية",
      "فداء"
    ],
    "answer": "صداقة",
    "exam": "الاختبار الثاني(المفردة الشاذة)البنك الأول",
    "category": "المفردة الشاذة"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 4,
    "question": "ما الكلمة المختلفة",
    "type": "اختيار",
    "choices": [
      "نجوم",
      "شمس",
      "سراج",
      "شموع"
    ],
    "answer": "نجوم",
    "exam": "الاختبار الثاني(المفردة الشاذة)البنك الأول",
    "category": "المفردة الشاذة"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 5,
    "question": "ما الكلمة المختلفة",
    "type": "اختيار",
    "choices": [
      "غواص",
      "مرجان",
      "شُعب",
      "نجم البحر"
    ],
    "answer": "غواص",
    "exam": "الاختبار الثاني(المفردة الشاذة)البنك الأول",
    "category": "المفردة الشاذة"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 6,
    "question": "ما الكلمة المختلفة",
    "type": "اختيار",
    "choices": [
      "الأحد",
      "الاثنين",
      "الثلاثاء",
      "الخميس"
    ],
    "answer": "الخميس",
    "exam": "الاختبار الثاني(المفردة الشاذة)البنك الأول",
    "category": "المفردة الشاذة"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 7,
    "question": "ما الكلمة المختلفة",
    "type": "اختيار",
    "choices": [
      "يجري( يركض)",
      "يمشي",
      "يقفز",
      "يطير"
    ],
    "answer": "يطير",
    "exam": "الاختبار الثاني(المفردة الشاذة)البنك الأول",
    "category": "المفردة الشاذة"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 8,
    "question": "ما الكلمة المختلفة",
    "type": "اختيار",
    "choices": [
      "قفز",
      "طيران",
      "ركض",
      "مشي"
    ],
    "answer": "طيران",
    "exam": "الاختبار الثاني(المفردة الشاذة)البنك الأول",
    "category": "المفردة الشاذة"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 9,
    "question": "ما الكلمة المختلفة",
    "type": "اختيار",
    "choices": [
      "قراءة",
      "نسخ",
      "كتابة",
      "رسم"
    ],
    "answer": "قراءة",
    "exam": "الاختبار الثاني(المفردة الشاذة)البنك الأول",
    "category": "المفردة الشاذة"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 10,
    "question": "ما الكلمة المختلفة",
    "type": "اختيار",
    "choices": [
      "قرأ",
      "نسخ",
      "كتب",
      "رسم"
    ],
    "answer": "قرأ",
    "exam": "الاختبار الثاني(المفردة الشاذة)البنك الأول",
    "category": "المفردة الشاذة"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 11,
    "question": "ما الكلمة المختلفة",
    "type": "اختيار",
    "choices": [
      "قميص",
      "ثوب",
      "سروال",
      "عمامة"
    ],
    "answer": "عمامة",
    "exam": "الاختبار الثاني(المفردة الشاذة)البنك الأول",
    "category": "المفردة الشاذة"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 12,
    "question": "ما الكلمة المختلفة",
    "type": "اختيار",
    "choices": [
      "حليب",
      "بيض",
      "سكر",
      "عسل"
    ],
    "answer": "سكر",
    "exam": "الاختبار الثاني(المفردة الشاذة)البنك الأول",
    "category": "المفردة الشاذة"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 13,
    "question": "ما الكلمة المختلفة",
    "type": "اختيار",
    "choices": [
      "دعاء",
      "صوم",
      "زكاة",
      "طواف"
    ],
    "answer": "دعاء",
    "exam": "الاختبار الثاني(المفردة الشاذة)البنك الأول",
    "category": "المفردة الشاذة"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 14,
    "question": "ما الكلمة المختلفة",
    "type": "اختيار",
    "choices": [
      "عين",
      "أنف",
      "فم",
      "ذقن"
    ],
    "answer": "ذقن",
    "exam": "الاختبار الثاني(المفردة الشاذة)البنك الأول",
    "category": "المفردة الشاذة"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 15,
    "question": "ما الكلمة المختلفة",
    "type": "اختيار",
    "choices": [
      "أبوة",
      "عمومة",
      "خؤولة",
      "بنوة"
    ],
    "answer": "بنوة",
    "exam": "الاختبار الثاني(المفردة الشاذة)البنك الأول",
    "category": "المفردة الشاذة"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 16,
    "question": "ما الكلمة المختلفة",
    "type": "اختيار",
    "choices": [
      "سيارة",
      "محرك",
      "مقود",
      "عجلات"
    ],
    "answer": "سيارة",
    "exam": "الاختبار الثاني(المفردة الشاذة)البنك الأول",
    "category": "المفردة الشاذة"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 17,
    "question": "ما الكلمة المختلفة",
    "type": "اختيار",
    "choices": [
      "عن",
      "في",
      "على",
      "إلا"
    ],
    "answer": "إلا",
    "exam": "الاختبار الثاني(المفردة الشاذة)البنك الأول",
    "category": "المفردة الشاذة"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 18,
    "question": "ما الكلمة المختلفة",
    "type": "اختيار",
    "choices": [
      "دراجة",
      "قطار",
      "سيارة",
      "حافلة"
    ],
    "answer": "دراجة",
    "exam": "الاختبار الثاني(المفردة الشاذة)البنك الأول",
    "category": "المفردة الشاذة"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 19,
    "question": "ما الكلمة المختلفة",
    "type": "اختيار",
    "choices": [
      "قلم",
      "دفتر",
      "مسطرة",
      "حاسوب"
    ],
    "answer": "حاسوب",
    "exam": "الاختبار الثاني(المفردة الشاذة)البنك الأول",
    "category": "المفردة الشاذة"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 20,
    "question": "ما الكلمة المختلفة",
    "type": "اختيار",
    "choices": [
      "حاسب آلي",
      "قلم",
      "كتاب",
      "مسطرة"
    ],
    "answer": "حاسب آلي",
    "exam": "الاختبار الثاني(المفردة الشاذة)البنك الأول",
    "category": "المفردة الشاذة"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 21,
    "question": "ما الكلمة المختلفة",
    "type": "اختيار",
    "choices": [
      "فرس",
      "ناقة",
      "أتان",
      "زرافة"
    ],
    "answer": "زرافة",
    "exam": "الاختبار الثاني(المفردة الشاذة)البنك الأول",
    "category": "المفردة الشاذة"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 22,
    "question": "ما الكلمة المختلفة",
    "type": "اختيار",
    "choices": [
      "لبؤة",
      "زرافة",
      "أتان",
      "فرس"
    ],
    "answer": "لبؤة",
    "exam": "الاختبار الثاني(المفردة الشاذة)البنك الأول",
    "category": "المفردة الشاذة"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 23,
    "question": "ما الكلمة المختلفة",
    "type": "اختيار",
    "choices": [
      "لبؤة",
      "أسد",
      "زرافة",
      "مهرة"
    ],
    "answer": "أسد",
    "exam": "الاختبار الثاني(المفردة الشاذة)البنك الأول",
    "category": "المفردة الشاذة"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 24,
    "question": "ما الكلمة المختلفة",
    "type": "اختيار",
    "choices": [
      "ناقة",
      "لبؤة",
      "أتان",
      "فرس"
    ],
    "answer": "لبؤة",
    "exam": "الاختبار الثاني(المفردة الشاذة)البنك الأول",
    "category": "المفردة الشاذة"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 25,
    "question": "ما الكلمة المختلفة",
    "type": "اختيار",
    "choices": [
      "حصان",
      "لبؤة",
      "زرافة",
      "أتان"
    ],
    "answer": "لبؤة",
    "exam": "الاختبار الثاني(المفردة الشاذة)البنك الأول",
    "category": "المفردة الشاذة"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 26,
    "question": "ما الكلمة المختلفة",
    "type": "اختيار",
    "choices": [
      "أسد",
      "لبؤة",
      "فرس",
      "ناقة"
    ],
    "answer": "أسد",
    "exam": "الاختبار الثاني(المفردة الشاذة)البنك الأول",
    "category": "المفردة الشاذة"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 27,
    "question": "ما الكلمة المختلفة",
    "type": "اختيار",
    "choices": [
      "أستاذ مساعد",
      "أستاذ",
      "أستاذ مشارك",
      "معلم"
    ],
    "answer": "معلم",
    "exam": "الاختبار الثاني(المفردة الشاذة)البنك الأول",
    "category": "المفردة الشاذة"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 28,
    "question": "ما الكلمة المختلفة",
    "type": "اختيار",
    "choices": [
      "تسويف",
      "تشبيه",
      "تقريب",
      "تمثيل"
    ],
    "answer": "تسويف",
    "exam": "الاختبار الثاني(المفردة الشاذة)البنك الأول",
    "category": "المفردة الشاذة"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 29,
    "question": "ما الكلمة المختلفة",
    "type": "اختيار",
    "choices": [
      "التشبيه",
      "التخويف",
      "التمثيل",
      "التقريب"
    ],
    "answer": "التخويف",
    "exam": "الاختبار الثاني(المفردة الشاذة)البنك الأول",
    "category": "المفردة الشاذة"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 30,
    "question": "ما الكلمة المختلفة",
    "type": "اختيار",
    "choices": [
      "باهظ",
      "ثمين",
      "كثير",
      "غالي"
    ],
    "answer": "كثير",
    "exam": "الاختبار الثاني(المفردة الشاذة)البنك الأول",
    "category": "المفردة الشاذة"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 31,
    "question": "ما الكلمة المختلفة",
    "type": "اختيار",
    "choices": [
      "بر",
      "دقيق",
      "طحين",
      "عجين"
    ],
    "answer": "عجين",
    "exam": "الاختبار الثاني(المفردة الشاذة)البنك الأول",
    "category": "المفردة الشاذة"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 32,
    "question": "ما الكلمة المختلفة",
    "type": "اختيار",
    "choices": [
      "مكتبة",
      "مجلة",
      "كتاب",
      "بحث"
    ],
    "answer": "مكتبة",
    "exam": "الاختبار الثاني(المفردة الشاذة)البنك الأول",
    "category": "المفردة الشاذة"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 33,
    "question": "ما الكلمة المختلفة",
    "type": "اختيار",
    "choices": [
      "مجلة",
      "جريدة",
      "وسيلة",
      "صحيفة"
    ],
    "answer": "وسيلة",
    "exam": "الاختبار الثاني(المفردة الشاذة)البنك الأول",
    "category": "المفردة الشاذة"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 34,
    "question": "ما الكلمة المختلفة",
    "type": "اختيار",
    "choices": [
      "هدية",
      "نفقة",
      "هبة",
      "عطية"
    ],
    "answer": "نفقة",
    "exam": "الاختبار الثاني(المفردة الشاذة)البنك الأول",
    "category": "المفردة الشاذة"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 35,
    "question": "ما الكلمة المختلفة",
    "type": "اختيار",
    "choices": [
      "ليل",
      "عصر",
      "فجر",
      "ظهر"
    ],
    "answer": "ليل",
    "exam": "الاختبار الثاني(المفردة الشاذة)البنك الأول",
    "category": "المفردة الشاذة"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 36,
    "question": "ما الكلمة المختلفة",
    "type": "اختيار",
    "choices": [
      "شجاع",
      "المحسن",
      "الكريم",
      "الجود"
    ],
    "answer": "الجود",
    "exam": "الاختبار الثاني(المفردة الشاذة)البنك الأول",
    "category": "المفردة الشاذة"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 37,
    "question": "ما الكلمة المختلفة",
    "type": "اختيار",
    "choices": [
      "المحسن",
      "المسيء",
      "المسامح",
      "المعاتب"
    ],
    "answer": "المسيء",
    "exam": "الاختبار الثاني(المفردة الشاذة)البنك الأول",
    "category": "المفردة الشاذة"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 38,
    "question": "ما الكلمة المختلفة",
    "type": "اختيار",
    "choices": [
      "لسن",
      "مهذار",
      "بليغ",
      "فصيح"
    ],
    "answer": "مهذار",
    "exam": "الاختبار الثاني(المفردة الشاذة)البنك الأول",
    "category": "المفردة الشاذة"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 39,
    "question": "ما الكلمة المختلفة",
    "type": "اختيار",
    "choices": [
      "قصة",
      "رواية",
      "أدب",
      "أقصوصة"
    ],
    "answer": "أدب",
    "exam": "الاختبار الثاني(المفردة الشاذة)البنك الأول",
    "category": "المفردة الشاذة"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 40,
    "question": "ما الكلمة المختلفة",
    "type": "اختيار",
    "choices": [
      "صُم",
      "قـُم",
      "نَم",
      "تَم"
    ],
    "answer": "تَم",
    "exam": "الاختبار الثاني(المفردة الشاذة)البنك الأول",
    "category": "المفردة الشاذة"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 41,
    "question": "ما الكلمة المختلفة",
    "type": "اختيار",
    "choices": [
      "سقف",
      "باب",
      "جدار",
      "شجرة"
    ],
    "answer": "شجرة",
    "exam": "الاختبار الثاني(المفردة الشاذة)البنك الأول",
    "category": "المفردة الشاذة"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 42,
    "question": "ما الكلمة المختلفة",
    "type": "اختيار",
    "choices": [
      "تجارة",
      "نماء",
      "بذخ",
      "زيادة"
    ],
    "answer": "بذخ",
    "exam": "الاختبار الثاني(المفردة الشاذة)البنك الأول",
    "category": "المفردة الشاذة"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 43,
    "question": "ما الكلمة المختلفة",
    "type": "اختيار",
    "choices": [
      "فوران",
      "غليان",
      "فيضان",
      "انصهار"
    ],
    "answer": "انصهار",
    "exam": "الاختبار الثاني(المفردة الشاذة)البنك الأول",
    "category": "المفردة الشاذة"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 44,
    "question": "ما الكلمة المختلفة",
    "type": "اختيار",
    "choices": [
      "فوران",
      "غليان",
      "فيضان",
      "ذوبان"
    ],
    "answer": "ذوبان",
    "exam": "الاختبار الثاني(المفردة الشاذة)البنك الأول",
    "category": "المفردة الشاذة"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 45,
    "question": "ما الكلمة المختلفة",
    "type": "اختيار",
    "choices": [
      "سفر",
      "فندق",
      "راحة",
      "سياحة"
    ],
    "answer": "سياحة",
    "exam": "الاختبار الثاني(المفردة الشاذة)البنك الأول",
    "category": "المفردة الشاذة"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 46,
    "question": "ما الكلمة المختلفة",
    "type": "اختيار",
    "choices": [
      "حج",
      "سعي",
      "طواف",
      "رمي"
    ],
    "answer": "حج",
    "exam": "الاختبار الثاني(المفردة الشاذة)البنك الأول",
    "category": "المفردة الشاذة"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 47,
    "question": "ما الكلمة المختلفة",
    "type": "اختيار",
    "choices": [
      "نجم",
      "ليل",
      "شرق",
      "غرب"
    ],
    "answer": "ليل",
    "exam": "الاختبار الثاني(المفردة الشاذة)البنك الأول",
    "category": "المفردة الشاذة"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 48,
    "question": "ما الكلمة المختلفة",
    "type": "اختيار",
    "choices": [
      "نظارة",
      "ساعة",
      "حذاء",
      "رداء"
    ],
    "answer": "ساعة",
    "exam": "الاختبار الثاني(المفردة الشاذة)البنك الأول",
    "category": "المفردة الشاذة"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 49,
    "question": "ما الكلمة المختلفة",
    "type": "اختيار",
    "choices": [
      "غرفة",
      "شقة",
      "بيت",
      "عمارة"
    ],
    "answer": "غرفة",
    "exam": "الاختبار الثاني(المفردة الشاذة)البنك الأول",
    "category": "المفردة الشاذة"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 50,
    "question": "ما الكلمة المختلفة",
    "type": "اختيار",
    "choices": [
      "الرئتين",
      "القلب",
      "العين",
      "الكبد"
    ],
    "answer": "العين",
    "exam": "الاختبار الثاني(المفردة الشاذة)البنك الأول",
    "category": "المفردة الشاذة"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 51,
    "question": "ما الكلمة المختلفة",
    "type": "اختيار",
    "choices": [
      "حشد",
      "جماعة",
      "سرب",
      "قادات"
    ],
    "answer": "قادات",
    "exam": "الاختبار الثاني(المفردة الشاذة)البنك الأول",
    "category": "المفردة الشاذة"
  },
  {
    "question_number": 52,
    "question": "ما الكلمة المختلفة",
    "type": "اختيار",
    "choices": [
      "منهاج (نهج)",
      "طريق",
      "درب (سبيل )",
      "وضوح"
    ],
    "answer": "وضوح",
    "exam": "الاختبار الثاني(المفردة الشاذة)البنك الأول",
    "category": "المفردة الشاذة"
  }
]
